callhunter.com 2017-05-11

# Privacy Policy - CallHunter

### Information Collection and Use

We receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with us. CallHunter and its authorized agents automatically receive and record "traffic data" on their server logs from your browser including your IP address, cookie information, and the page you requested. 

### Communications from the Site

Generally, CallHunter does not initiate communication with users. Service related announcements will be made through the site itself on its homepage or similarly recognizable location. 

### Information Sharing and Disclosure

We may release personal information when we believe in good faith that release is necessary to comply with a law; to enforce or apply our Terms of Use and other policies; or to protect the rights, property, or safety of the Company, our employees, our users, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud and risk protection. 

### Cookies

A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user’s computer for record-keeping purposes. We use cookies on this site. We do not link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our site. 

We use both session ID cookies and persistent cookies. We use session cookies to make it easier for you to navigate our site. A session ID cookie expires when you close your browser. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time. You can remove persistent cookies by following directions provided in your Internet browser’s “help” file. 

Persistent cookies enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site. 

If you reject cookies, you may still use our site, but your ability to use some areas of our site will be limited. 

Some of our business partners (e.g., advertisers) use cookies on our site. We have no access to or control over these cookies. 

This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by CallHunter only and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers. 

### Bulletin Boards/Chat Rooms

If you use a bulletin board or chat room on this site, you should be aware that any personally identifiable information you submit there can be read, collected, or used by other users of these forums, and could be used to send you unsolicited messages. We are not responsible for the personally identifiable information you choose to submit in these forums. 

### Links to Other Sites

This Web site contains links to other sites that are not owned or controlled by CallHunter. Please be aware that we, CallHunter, are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. 

We encourage you to be aware when you leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. 

This privacy statement applies only to information collected by this Web site. 

### Children Under 18 Years of Age

CallHunter does not specifically collect information about children. If we learn that CallHunter has collected information from a child under the age of 13, we will delete that information as quickly as possible. 

### Changes in this Privacy Statement

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. 

We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page. 

### Contact Us

If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us at: [privacy@callhunter.com](mailto:privacy@callhunter.com)
